

Personal

Address
 No 17 Ohiamini road, Psychiatric Rumuigbo,
 Port Harcourt

Port Harcourt 500272 Phone number

09026023408

Email kizidon2006@gmail.com

Date of birth 14-06-1993

Place of birth Port Harcourt

Mationality Nigeria

Driving licence

Go LinkedIn Kzito Amuka

Interests

 Hiking, Surfing the Internet, Publishing News on my blog, Driving

Languages

Igbo language



I am a flexible and experienced advertising administrator also experienced in Information Communication and Technology with excellent time management skills, i create websites, Blogs and also a Social Media Influences that could enable you sell your products and services on any platform. I am also an experienced event planner and have worked as an Event Manager in a 3 star Hotel. I am a good communicator with proven inter personal skills and am used to working in a team whilst also being capable of using own initiative. I am skilled In dealing with problems in a resourceful manner and negotiating to achieve beneficial agreement. I am always enthusiastic to learn and undertake new challenges.

Work experience

Event Manager Mar 2019 - Dec 2020

De Lasmall Hotel Nigeria Ltd., Port Harcourt

ICT administrator Jul 2017 - Jan 2019

KZ Technical Co NIG ltd., Port Harcourt

Education and Qualifications

Bachelor of Science Sep 2012 - Jul 2016

Imo state University, Owerri

Sep 2020 - Jul 2020

References

References available on request.

Skills

Microsoft Word

Website Developer

Event Planning

Courses

HSE 1,2, 3 Nov 2019 - Dec 2019

Onshore and Offshore Safety Institute of Nigeria

Advanced HSE Nov 2020 - Dec 2020

Onshore and Offshore Institute

General Health safety and Environment Course May 2019 - Jun 2019

Maritime Academy of Nigeria

Stew Basic Safety Training Jun 2019 - Jul 2019

Maritime Academy of Nigeria